# Victor Zhang

male | Single | Born in 1990/9 | HUKOU: BEIJING

Location: OVERSEAS-

>2 Years' Experience | Have Overseas Work | Citizenship

Passport: G61708121

18601024483

E-mail: victorinhollywood@gmail.com

# Career Objective

Desired Type of Employment:

Full-time, Intern

Desired Position:

Films/Media/Publication/Printing

Desired Industry:

Advertising/Exhibitions/Public Relations, Other, Computer Software, Internet/E-Commerce,

Media/Publication/Films

Desired Location:

BEIJING, United States

Expected Salary (before tax):

Confidential

# Self-assessment

I Have Two years experience in the Student Union at my University, One year school assistant work experience, one year Apple retail store work experience, training a lot of social intercourse and commu nication skills, stronger eloquence skills, have ability with all types of people and customers to es tablished friendly relations; ability to resolve any matter with independent analytical. Studying Ma in Major-Film, beginning at college, five years relevant professional system learning, film enthusia sts, open-minded, flexible thinking, great film industry practice during at graduate work. Proficient in PC or Mac, Professional proficiency in the use of a variety of editing software (Final Cut Pro, Avid, Premiere etc.), Productivity Software (Office, iWork), at the same time to grasp Photoshop, AE, Maya, 3Dmax, Nuke, etc.

#### Project Experience

2012/05 -- 2013/08

Apple

Responsibilities (your responsibilities and achievements):

 ${\tt Specialist}$ 

2011/10 -- 2012/01

XingXing International Education

Responsibilities (your responsibilities and achievements):

Teaching Assistant



### Education Background

2013/09-- 2014/10

New York Film Academy | Directing | Master

2009/09-- 2013/06

The Capital Normal University Of KEDE College | Radio and Television Editing &

Directing | Bachelor

2006/06-- 2009/09

Ritan Middle School | aa | Senior High

Graduates Info.

College 1st Prize

Social Events

2014/07 -- 2014/07

NYFA Thesis Film -2930

My personal Independent Film, Production by New York Film Academy, Credit is Director, producer and screenwriter.

2014/07 -- 2014/07

NYFA Thesis Film - MeiMei

A Film Production by New York Film Academy, Credit is the 2nd AC.

2014/07 -- 2014/07

NYFA Thesis Film —For You

A Film Production by New York Film Academy, Credit is the Key Grip.

2014/06 -- 2014/06

NYFA Thesis Film -Pretty canned

A Film Production by New York Film Academy, Credit is the Key Grip.

2001/05 -- 2001/09

Television Of KEDE

2001/05 -- 2001/09

Television Of KEDE

2001/06 -- 2001/10

Campus Reporter

2009/07 -- 2009/08

Volunteer of Italian Super Cup

NYFA Thesis Film - Monday 3PM

A Film Production by New York Film Academy, Credit is Grip.

```
2014/10 -- 2014/10
```

```
NYFA Thesis Film -Lost Angel
```

A Film Production by New York Film Academy, Credit is 1st AD.

2014/08 -- 2014/08

# NYFA Thesis Film - The 3rd Man

A Film Production by New York Film Academy, Credit is Gaffer.

2014/08 -- 2014/08

#### NYFA Thesis Film - Psychologist

A Film Production by New York Film Academy, Credit is the Key Grip.

2008/07 -- 2008/09

Youth Volunteer of The 29th Summer Olympic Games

# Training

2012/12--2013/02

Apple Inc.

Training Course: Apple Global retail development

Training Location: Beijing

2010/06--2011/12

Beijing Xing Xing International Animation Education

Training Course: 3D modeling Training Location: Beijing

## Certificates

2012/01

Nationwide Lawyer Certificate

# Language Skills

English: reading&writing proficient listening&speaking proficient

#### Professional Skills

```
MAYA | basic | 12
Final Cut Pro | proficient | 24
iWork | proficient | 24
Microsoft Office | proficient | 24
```